<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>It's All About the Kung-Fu</title>
  <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/</link>
  <description>or How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love My Green Belt</description>
  <generator>BlazeBlogger 1.0.0</generator>
  <item>
    <title>the percipio project</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/05/26-percipio_project/</link>
    <description>
i needed a project to recentre myself given the current load of inanity in my
life right now, and a project came up that should provide just that. essentially, i will be designing and building my own 16-bit computer based on
the book The Elements of Computing Systems. the book is geared towards simulating the computer using the tools provided
(such as a hardware simulator based on their easy to learn / use HDL) but i've decided the project would be far more satisfying if i actually built the
co    </description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>settting a remote git repo: notes</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/05/25-remote_git/</link>
    <description>
github is a very useful service but very limiting
for private repositories with collaborators. there are a few things you need
to do differently, and a remote repo shouldn't be used for a work environment. the basic requirements are a locally-hosted repo with code and a committed working tree
a place to store the remote repo accessible via ssh the first thing we need to do is to make sure that if it isn't already,
the local repo should be committed and clean. $ git commit -a now we need to set     </description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Learning Android</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/04/24-learning-android/</link>
    <description>
I just started reading the book Learning Android.
The book relies heavily on using the Eclipse IDE, but as we know Eclipse is
proof that Shaitan hates us and wants us to be miserable, I'm working through
the book using netbeans. I'm going to try to start documenting my adventures
working with android in netbeans. The interested can follow along.
    </description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>rawk</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/02/23-rawk_released/</link>
    <description>
For a long time, building my personal site was painful, simply because I
didn't need (or want) a large framework or dynamic content or anything
fancy, just a few simple static pages. I was hand-writing them all, which
meant that given how little I enjoyed doing that, pages weren't ever really
getting updated and you can pretty much forget adding much in the way of new
content. I decided to do something about this, and spent a week or two writing rawk. rawk stands for 'rage against web framework    </description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>mutt and gmail</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/01/21-mutt_and_gmail/</link>
    <description>I wanted to set up mutt to work with gmail. Here's a quick post talking
about what you need to have to get IMAP and SMTPS working with mutt. For
reference, I've been using my google apps email and not just a plain gmail address.
    </description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cleaning Up the Music Library</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/01/22-dedup_py/</link>
    <description>A while ago, I made the mistake of using iTunes for my music library;
when I wanted to move my music from my interla hard drive to the external
drive, I ran into some issues. Namely, the migration (using the iTunes set
library location followed by a 'organise library') failed multiple times.
I ended up with lots of duplicate songs.
    </description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>converting AAC to mp3 in debian squeeze</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/01/20-aac2mp3-squeeze/</link>
    <description>I recently installed Debian squeeze on my eeepc (a subject for another
post). The install is a development install, and everyone knows one of the
most useful things for development is a feed of good music. I keep a small
music library on the machine and use cmus, a console mp3 player, to play music. Unfortunately, the version
installed in Debian Squeeze doesn't seem to support AAC. I set out to figure
out how to convert my AAC files to mp3 files.
    </description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>new take on spam</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/01/19-new_take_on_spam/</link>
    <description>I hadn't seen this approach to the Nigerian scams before...
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Building an Inline Sniffer using a Guru Server Plus</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2011/01/18-guruplug_sniffing_bridge/</link>
    <description>I recently purchased a Global Scale Technologies Guru Server Plus
to use as a sort of rogue-box system for security research and CTF games.
Braving my distaste for Linux, I installed Debian on the box using
Bernd Zeimetz's excellent article Installing Debian on the Guruplug Server Plus. I ended up installing
twice due to deviations from the instructions; the instructions do work when followed. You will need a JTAG adapter to
install Debian. I'm not sure how well these instructions will apply to
    </description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Compiling Source Navigator in Ubuntu 10.04</title>
    <link>http://www.kyleisom.net/blog/2010/07/17-20100724_ubuntu-snav/</link>
    <description>Compiling source navigator under Ubuntu 10.04 is fairly easy once you
get the dependencies down. Grab the source from the sourceforge page.
The dependencies you need are: tk tklib libx11-dev libxmu-dev libxmu-headers libxt-dev libtool Of course you also need build-essential. Then a quick ./configure --prefix=/opt/source-nav
make
sudo make install should do the trick.     </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>